<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/introduction/</guid><description>Get started Navigate to the GitHub application page for Githaxs. Click on Install or Configure. Select the GitHub Organization you want to install the application on. Select either All repositories or Only select repositories; if the latter select which repositories you wish to install the application on. Click Install.</description></item><item><title>Configuration</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/configuration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/configuration/</guid><description>👉 You must be an admin in your GitHub Organization to install or configure Tasks. After installing the Githaxs Application certain tasks will start running by default on your entire organization. You will be re-directed to my.githaxs.com where you can update task configurations for your GitHub Organization.
Task Installation A task can be configured to run in multiple different ways providing you maximum flexibility and convenience.
The first option is to install a task on your Entire Org.</description></item><item><title>Migration</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/migration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/migration/</guid><description>How do I Migrate? Migrating to Githaxs is a lot easier than migrating between other CI/CD providers. When migrating to Githaxs there is no need to translate between Jenkins and CircleCI syntax or to contact us for a migration plan.
Migration is a three-step process:
Install Githaxs Application.
Delete CI tasks from your current CI tooling.
Configure Githaxs tasks.</description></item><item><title>Security</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/security/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/security/</guid><description>Our Practices You can view our Security Policies and Procedures that are followed at Githaxs.</description></item></channel></rss>