<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/introduction/</guid><description>Get started Githaxs provides two different GitHub Applications: Githaxs Meta and Githaxs.
The Githaxs Meta application does not have access to your application source code. It performs checks on and tasks based on Meta data (i.e. checking Pull Request Title, size of PR, etc).
The Githaxs application does have access to your application source code. It performs tasks such as linting, static scanning, and running unit tests.
Install Application Installation of either Githaxs application is done with a few clicks of a button.</description></item><item><title>Migration</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/migration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/migration/</guid><description>How do I Migrate? Migrating to Githaxs is a lot easier than migrating between other CI/CD providers. When migrating to Githaxs there is no need to translate between Jenkins and CircleCI syntax.
Here is the three step process:
Install Githaxs Application.
Create githaxs_settings/ghx.yml configuration file.
Delete CI tasks from your current CI tooling (optional)</description></item><item><title>Security</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/security/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/security/</guid><description>Our Practices Secure Webhooks To limit the requests our platform receives we have followed the guide GitHub offers for Securing your webhooks. We validate the signature of every request and reject the requests which have not been signed with a secret token.
Data Protection To ensure the protection of your data we ensure all data is encrypted at rest and in transit. Additionally, any tasks which clone GitHub repositories store the cloned repo in ephemeral storage and explicitly delete the repository as an extra precaution after the task has completed.</description></item></channel></rss>