<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/introduction/</guid><description>Get started The first step is to install the Githaxs application.
Navigate to the GitHub application page for Githaxs or Githaxs Workflow. Click on Install or Configure. Select the GitHub Organization you want to install the application on. Select either All repositories or Only select repositories; if the latter select which repositories you wish to install the application on. Note both Githaxs applications are configured from a repository named githaxs_settings within your organization.</description></item><item><title>Configuration</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/configuration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/configuration/</guid><description>Both Githaxs applications are configured from a repo named githaxs_settings with a file named ghx.yml.
👉 Configurations are read from githaxs_setting/ghx.yml. After you install the Githaxs Applications in your GitHub Organization, you can start configuring tasks to run on your repositories. A task can be configured to run on a repo in multiple different ways providing you maximum flexibility and convenience.
Org Setting this key to true will enable a task to run on every repository you installed the GitHub Application on in the Getting Started steps.</description></item><item><title>Migration</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/migration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/migration/</guid><description>How do I Migrate? Migrating to Githaxs is a lot easier than migrating between other CI/CD providers. When migrating to Githaxs there is no need to translate between Jenkins and CircleCI syntax.
Here is the three step process:
Install Githaxs Application.
Create githaxs_settings/ghx.yml configuration file.
Delete CI tasks from your current CI tooling (optional)</description></item><item><title>Security</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/security/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/getting-started/security/</guid><description>Our Practices You can view our Security Policies and Procedures that are followed at Githaxs.</description></item></channel></rss>