<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tasks on</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/</link><description>Recent content in Tasks on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Code Freeze</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/code-freeze/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/code-freeze/</guid><description>Code Freeze Allows you to prevent deployents during sensitive times/days of the year.
If you&amp;rsquo;re an e-commerce company you may want to restrict deployments just before Black Friday or your biggest sales day of the year. Perhaps you want a relaxing holiday for your employees over Christmas and New Years. Maybe you don&amp;rsquo;t want to deploy on weekends. Whatever the case may be, you can enforce these restrictions with this task.</description></item><item><title>PR Too Big</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/pr-too-big/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/pr-too-big/</guid><description>PR Too Big Atlassian, Small Business Programming, and Google have made the case for using small pull requests to improve team efficiency and reduce errors.
PR Too Big will programatically enforce keeping pull requests small while also providing an override feature.
Configuration parameter description required default max_changed_files The maximum number of changed files in a pull request no 0 max_additions The maximum number of additions in a pull request as calculated by GitHub no 0 max_deletions The maximum number of deletions in a pull request as calculated by GitHub no 0 Example Configuration # githaxs_settings/ghx.</description></item><item><title>Prettier</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/prettier/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/prettier/</guid><description>Prettier Prettier is an opinionated code formatter created to reduce time spent deliberating over which style conventions to use.
This task ensures all files are formatted with prettier and allows you to create globally shared configurations.
Configuration parameter description required prettier_config A map of prettier options True Example Configuration # githaxs_settings/ghx.yml prettier: settings: org: # Cannot be overriden by repo specific settings final: prettier_config: singleQuote: true semi: false # Default value if repo specific settings do not exist default: prettier_config: singleQuote: true semi: false</description></item><item><title>Title Lint</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/title-lint/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/title-lint/</guid><description>Title Lint Title Lint ensures all Pull Request titles follow a similar pattern.
This application is useful if you follow standards such as conventional commit or as part of your change managegment process to ensure Pull Requests are linked back to your work management tool (i.e. Jira).
Configuration parameter description required regex The regular expression to test Pull Request titles agains yes exclude_users A list of users to exclude from checking Pull Request Titles (i.</description></item></channel></rss>