<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tasks on</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/</link><description>Recent content in Tasks on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Code Freeze</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/workflow/code-freeze/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/workflow/code-freeze/</guid><description>Allows you to prevent deployents during sensitive times/days of the year.
If you&amp;rsquo;re an e-commerce company you may want to restrict deployments just before Black Friday or your biggest sales day of the year. Perhaps you want a relaxing holiday for your employees over Christmas and New Years. Maybe you don&amp;rsquo;t want to deploy on weekends. Whatever the case may be, you can enforce these restrictions with this task.</description></item><item><title>Hadolint</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/cq/hadolint/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/cq/hadolint/</guid><description> Hadolint helps you build Docker images that follow Best Practices
Example Configuration # githaxs_settings/ghx.yml hadolint: installation: org: true</description></item><item><title>PR Too Big</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/workflow/pr-too-big/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/workflow/pr-too-big/</guid><description>Atlassian, Small Business Programming, and Google have made the case for using small pull requests to improve team efficiency and reduce errors.
PR Too Big will programatically enforce keeping pull requests small while also providing an override feature.
Configuration parameter description required default max_changed_files The maximum number of changed files in a pull request no 0 max_additions The maximum number of additions in a pull request as calculated by GitHub no 0 max_deletions The maximum number of deletions in a pull request as calculated by GitHub no 0 Example Configuration # githaxs_settings/ghx.</description></item><item><title>Prettier</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/cq/prettier/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/cq/prettier/</guid><description>Prettier is an opinionated code formatter created to reduce time spent deliberating over which style conventions to use.
The Prettier Task ensures files are formatted properly. Now you can run Prettier on all of your Organizations repos with three lines of configuration.
Details File Extensions The Prettier task will only run on files that end with the following extensions: js, ts, scss, css, yaml, yml, html, jsx.
Files in Scope The Prettier task does not scan the entire repository, it only scans the files that have changed in a Pull Request.</description></item><item><title>Pylint</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/cq/pylint/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/cq/pylint/</guid><description>Pylint enforces the PEP8 style guide and detects errors in your Python code.
Details Files Scanned Files that end in .py and that have been changed in a Pull Request will be scanned. This task does not scan the entire repo.
Configuration The task does not support any custom configuration except for installing
Example Configuration # githaxs_settings/ghx.yml pylint: installation: org: true Bugs/Feature Requests Noticed a problem with this task or would like a new feature?</description></item><item><title>ShellCheck</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/cq/shellcheck/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/cq/shellcheck/</guid><description> ShellCheck finds bugs in your shell scripts. tests.
Details File Extensions ShellCheck will only run on files that end with .sh.
Files in Scope Only files that have changed in a Pull Request will be analyzed by this task.
Configuration There are currently no configuration options for ShellCheck other than to install it.
Example Configuration # githaxs_settings/ghx.yml shellcheck: installation: org: true</description></item><item><title>Terraform Format</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/cq/tf-fmt/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/cq/tf-fmt/</guid><description>Terraform Format is built into the Terraform binary and has an opinionated convention for how files should be formatted.
The Terraform Format Task ensures files are formatted properly.
Details File Extensions The task will only run on files that end with .tf and .tfvars
Files in Scope The Terraform Format task does not scan the entire repository, it only scans the files that have changed in a Pull Request.</description></item><item><title>Title Lint</title><link>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/workflow/title-lint/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.githaxs.com/docs/tasks/workflow/title-lint/</guid><description>Title Lint ensures all Pull Request titles follow a similar pattern.
This application is useful if you follow standards such as conventional commit or as part of your change managegment process to ensure Pull Requests are linked back to your work management tool (i.e. Jira).
Configuration parameter description required regex The regular expression to test Pull Request titles agains yes exclude_users A list of users to exclude from checking Pull Request Titles (i.</description></item></channel></rss>